Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - November 1975
    - Mikado, 751105 (Box 15)
    - Soccer vs. Brown, 751106 (Box 15)
    - Football vs. Brown, 751107 (Box 15)
    - Electric car, 751108 (Box 15)
    - John reich, 751109 (Box 15)
    - Quick Deposit Box, 751110 (Box 15)
    - Shah of Iran's sister, Princes Ashraf Pahlavi, 751111 (Box 15)
    - Black students protest meeting with Corson, 751112 (Box 15)
    - Alternatives Library, Annabel Taylor, 751113 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes, 751114 (Box 15)
    - Straight's 50th Birthday Party, 751115 (Box 15)
    - Jimmy Carter, former Governor of Georgia and Presidential candidate - at B & PA school, 751116 (Box 15)
    - Carolyn Adams, 751117 (Box 15)
    - David Rockefeller - B & PA Executive Forum, 751118 (Box 15)
  - December 1975
    - B & PA School, 751201 (Box 15)
    - Carolers singing to Corson, 751202 (Box 15)
    - Window decorated for Christmas at the Straight - also pine tree in front of Straight, 751203 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes (Sol), 751204 (Box 15)
    - Resler & Kosstrin with car, spark plugs and piston (emission control design), 751205 (Box 15)
    - Dr. wimsatt, 751206 (Box 15)
    - Special Faculty Meeting (Ky affair), 751207 (Box 15)
  - January 1976
    - Law School Still Life, 760101 (Box 15)
    - Peter Narins and frogs at Langmuir Lab, 760102 (Box 15)
    - Computer Dining, 760103 (Box 15)
    - Deferred Maintenance (Phillips Hall), 760104 (Box 15)
    - Vet School - horse imsemination, 760106 (Box 15)
    - Great Dane feeding study (Dr. Kirk), 760107 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes (snow), 760108 (Box 15)
    - Winter Scenes (lake), 760109 (Box 15)
    - John Hsu and rare books, 760110 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - winter, 760111 (Box 15)
    - Students return, 760112 (Box 15)
    - Bee-eater bird - slide copies, 760113 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - winter at the hydraulic plant (Steve Siegert & Howie Frisch), 760114 (Box 15)
    - Lincoln Center, 760115 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - winter, 760116 (Box 15)
  - February 1976
    - Old student scrapbooks from Archives, 760201 (Box 15)
    - Copy of photograph of Brancusi sculpture, 760202 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - winter, 760203 (Box 15)
    - Slide copy - colonial birds, 760204 (Box 15)
    - Mellissa Grant - student who spent 2 week study tour in Russia, 760205 (Box 15)
    - Visual Services office with new display panels, 760206 (Box 15)
    - Risley musical - "Stop the World", 760207 (Box 15)
    - Charlie Matthews - Judicial advisor, 760208 (Box 15)
    - Ceremony dedicating library to Lowell T. George of the Safety Division, 760209 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - Green Dragon, Zeus, Campus Store, Balch, geese and tower, 760210 (Box 15)
    - Bubblegum bubble contest, 760211 (Box 15)
  - March 1976
    - Vet School Mastitis Clinic (Land Grant), 760301A (Box 15)
    - Johnson Art Museum Art Awareness Program (Land Grant), 760301B (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes (long range lens), 760302 (Box 15)
    - Employee education program, 760303 (Box 15)
    - HEPS, 760304 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Gymnast, Cathy Danielski, 760305 (Box 15)
    - Boozer (dog) with pacemaker and his owners, Mr. And Mrs. Daisy, 760306 (Box 15)
    - Copy of old photo of Appledore Island, 760307 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - bagpipe player, 760308 (Box 15)
    - Aliza Tamir (profile), 760309 (Box 15)
    - Computer Graphics, 760310 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Figure Skating Club ice show (Lynah), 760311 (Box 15)
    - Surinder Sidhu, 760312 (Box 15)
    - Green Dragon Parade, 760313 (Box 15)
    - Maple Sugar production, Arnot Forest, 760314 (Box 15)
    - Donald Paterson - University organist, 760315 (Box 15)
    - Million Dollar Class Trophy, 760316 (Box 15)
    - Neptune Accelerator and students, 760317 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - Beebe Lake area, 760318 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - night on quad, 760319 (Box 15)
    - Floyd Newman donating old uniform, etc. to ROTC, 760320 (Box 15)
    - Pitambar Sharma Upadhyaya, graduate student from Nepal, 760321 (Box 15)
    - Jack Lowe and his model boats, 760322 (Box 15)
  - April 1976
    - Interlibrary loan program - Liverpool, N.Y. Iris Cohen (Land Grant), 760401A (Box 15)
    - Instructional TV Program - Corning Glass and Cornell (Land Grant), 760401B (Box 15)
    - Middle management program - Columbian Rope - Auburn, N.Y. (Land Grant), 760401C (Box 15)
    - Labor Studies Program - Buffalo - Sarah Vickars (Land Grant), 760401D (Box 15)
    - Historic Preservation - Watkins Glen - (Land Grant), 760401E (Box 15)
    - High Blood pressure Clinic - N.Y. Med. College (Land Grant), 760401F (Box 15)
    - COSEP - educational opportunities for minorities - Diane Clarke (Land Grant), 760401G (Box 15)
    - Magnolia Tree Center - Brooklyn, N.Y. (Land Grant), 760401H (Box 15)
    - Day Care Center - Nassau County (Land grant), 760401I (Box 15)
    - Suburban (Land Grant), 760401J (Box 15)
    - Insect control - Albion & Geneva, N.Y. (Land Grant), 760401K (Box 15)
    - Fishing Industry - Sea Grant, Greenport, L.I. (Land Grant), 760401L (Box 15)
    - Horse racing industry - Saratoga Springs (Land Grant), 760401M (Box 15)
    - EFNEP - Albany (Land grant), 760401N (Box 15)
    - Logging industry - Old Forge (Land Grant), 760401O (Box 15)
    - Coy negs. - Land grant Brochure sample pages - and photo of ten dollar bill, 760402 (Box 15)
    - Floyd Newman and Bob Kane at Schoellkopf Field House, 760403 (Box 15)
    - Indian Students' concert, 760404 (Box 15)
    - Richard Schultz, new athletic director, and Bob Kane, 760405 (Box 15)
    - N.Y. Convocation, 760406 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - clock faces, bikes, frisbee & spring shots, 760407 (Box 15)
    - Russian Choir, 760408 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Ag. Quad, Olin Library, 760409 (Box 15)
    - Black students rally in front of Straight and enter Day Hall, April 19, 1976, 760410 (Box 15)
    - Jim Oliver - profile, 760411 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - spring flowers, 760412 (Box 15)
    - Takeover of Admissions Building and photos of rooms inside Day Hall after takeover on same day, April 20, 1976, 760413 (Box 15)
    - Vet School Open House, 760414 (Box 15)
    - Africana Center, 760415 (Box 15)
    - Black March to Courthouse, 760416 (Box 15)
    - Engineering earthquake machine (Sol), 760417 (Box 15)
    - Tower Club Dinner, World Trade Center, New York City - April 29, 1976, 760418 (Box 15)
  - May 1976
    - Dr. Krook - Vet School, 760501 (Box 15)
    - Pigs, 760502 (Box 15)
    - Apple Blossoms, 760503 (Box 15)
    - Stanley Kaufmann at A.D. White House, 760504 (Box 15)
    - Campus Scenes - Statues, tower, 760505 (Box 15)
    - Risley Fair, 760506 (Box 15)
    - Cornell debaters - Denise Gilbert and Tom McCarthy, 760507 (Box 15)
    - Outstanding seniors - Bob Harrison and Kathleen Sullivan, 760508 (Box 15)
    - Lois Gray, new Assoc. Dean and Director Extension, 760509 (Box 15)
    - Electric car at Watkins Glen, 760510 (Box 15)
    - M. and Mrs. Bowmar, 760511 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse v. Hopkins, 760512 (Box 15)
    - Commencement, 760513 (Box 15)
    - President Corson resigns, 760514 (Box 15)
  - June 1976
    - Fog, 760601 (Box 15)
    - Giok Po Oey, 760602 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse v. Maryland (Championship game) (Bob Smith), 760603 (Box 15)
    - Giacometti sculpture at Art Museum, 760604 (Box 15)
    - George Ridenour and Sherri Coe - B & PA, 760605 (Box 15)
    - Dave Knapp and Robert Lindquist (check passing), 760606 (Box 15)
    - President Corson and check donation, 760607 (Box 15)
    - Reunion, 760608 (Box 15)
    - Alumnus John H. Astor donating Bennington flag to Cornell, 760609 (Box 15)
    - Floyd Newman with Bob Kane and trophies, 760610 (Box 15)
  - [none for July?]
    - Untitled (Box 15)
  - August 1976
    - Governor Carey visits Cornell, 760801 (Box 15)
    - Football player with head shaved except for "C", 760802 (Box 15)
    - Freshman games on quad (Offbeat Olympics), 760803 (Box 15)
  - September 1976
    - Darwin Williams, new director of COSEP, 760901 (Box 15)
    - Barefoot chime ringer, 760902 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - arriving freshmen, views from Tower, Baker, 760903 (Box 15)
    - New plaque at Oakenshields diningroom at Straight, 760904 (Box 15)
    - Registration, 760905 (Box 15)
    - Head Trainer Tom McGory working with a footballer, 760906 (Box 15)
    - Henry Orlov, visiting music prof., 760907 (Box 15)
    - Fun in the Sun Festival on Arts Quad, 760908 (Box 15)
    - Mr. McNair (Eben) - Development, 760909 (Box 15)
    - Meetings of Women Trustees (Sol), 760910 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Arts Quad and Sibley, 760911 (Box 15)
    - Africana Center, 760912 (Box 15)
    - Musicians rehearsing for Schubert Festival, 760913 (Box 15)
    - Windows, Goldwin Smith lecture room, campus scenes, 760914 (Box 15)
    - Football vs. Princeton, 760915 (Box 15)
    - Female ROTC cadets, 760916 (Box 15)
    - David and Mrs. Usher and parabolic receiver, 760917 (Box 15)
    - Henry Guerlac at A.D. White House, 760918 (Box 15)
    - Alan Sheppard - 44 year old businessman returns to live in frat., 760919 (Box 15)
    - Football vs. Colgate, 760921 (Box 15)
  - October 1976
    - Vet School (Sol), 761001 (Box 15)
    - Renee Hack, champion gymnast, 761002 (Box 15)
    - Fall In, 761003 (Box 15)
    - Dog with Narcophobia (sleeping illness), 761004 (Box 15)
    - Basketball players in Art Museum, 761005 (Box 15)
    - Outing Club Teepee and Roxanne Nersesian, club president, Mt. Pleasant, 761006 (Box 15)
    - Educational TV center, Martha Van, 761007 (Box 15)
    - Stephen Foley and Jay Cohen, student trustees, 761008 (Box 15)
    - Art's 40th birthday party, 761009 (Box 15)
    - Pile of paper clips - war on waste, 761010 (Box 15)
    - Fall scenes, 761011 (Box 15)
    - Dedication of oak trees to honor Nellie Corson, 761012 (Box 15)
    - F.R. Newman memorabilia cases, 761013 (Box 15)
    - Trustee Council weekend, October 23, 761014 (Box 15)
    - F.R. Newman dedication of military collection, 761015 (Box 15)
    - Students protesting with coffin, 761016 (Box 15)
    - Homecoming, 761017 (Box 15)
    - Floyd Newman album, 761018 (Box 15)
    - Library spook shots and rainy scenes, 761019 (Box 15)
    - Halloween Costumes, 761020 (Box 15)
  - November 1976
    - Lost keys, 761101 (Box 15)
    - Arecibo Radio telescope photos of Venus, 761102 (Box 15)
    - Daina Niparts, 761103 (Box 15)
    - Cornell Clippers, 761104 (Box 15)
    - Bob Smith, 761105 (Box 15)
    - Mario van Zendt, new COSEP director, 761106 (Box 15)
    - United Way, 761107 (Box 15)
    - Student police, 761108 (Box 15)
    - Wasted food in cafeterias, 761109 (Box 15)
    - Winter scenes, 761110 (Box 15)
    - Community Band at Museum (and leaf clean-up), 761111 (Box 15)
    - Dog house on engineering quad, 761112 (Box 15)
    - Grumann Squash Court dedication, 761113 (Box 15)
    - Family Day with Dave Knapp on K.P., 761114 (Box 15)
    - New COSEP Associate Director, 761115 (Box 15)
    - Snow Scenes, 761116 (Box 15)
    - Profile - Lou Pearsall, 761117 (Box 15)
  - December 1976
    - New Football coach, 761201 (Box 15)
    - New key registration system, 761202 (Box 15)
    - 150 lb. Football team pumps gas to earn money for trip to Japan, 761203 (Box 15)
    - B & PA tournament students, 761204 (Box 15)
    - Clarke Hall, 761205 (Box 15)
    - Bethe-Commoner debate, 761206 (Box 15)
    - Sage Chapel Christmas decorations, 761207 (Box 15)
    - Students studying, 761208 (Box 15)
    - Ben Mintz' retirement party, 761209 (Box 15)
    - Final exams, 761210 (Box 15)
    - Santa Claus over Arecibo, 761211 (Box 15)
  - January 1977
    - Hockey vs. Univ. of Vermont, 770101 (Box 15)
    - New wing dedication, Mallott Hall, 770102 (Box 15)
    - 150 lb. Football team in Japan, 770103 (Box 15)
    - B & PA tournament, 770104 (Box 15)
    - Jack Lowe and his model boats, 770105 (Box 15)
    - Winter scenes, 770106 (Box 15)
    - Bailey Hall - empty, 770107 (Box 15)
    - Underwater pool shots (S. Siegert), 770108 (Box 15)
    - Student head shots - registration, 770109 (Box 15)
    - Jack Lowe's model boats (macro shots), 770110 (Box 15)
    - Winter scenes, 770111 (Box 15)
  - February 1977
    - Tom Leavitt, Museum Director, 770201 (Box 15)
    - Hans Bethe and Peierls, 770202 (Box 15)
    - Sage diningroom (before renovation), 770203 (Box 15)
    - Cooking over fire at Japes lodge, 770204 (Box 15)
    - Landscape architecture students with winning playground design, 770205 (Box 15)
    - Lady bus driver (Marian Hansen), 770206 (Box 15)
    - Women's basketball team returns from being snowed in, 770207 (Box 15)
    - Dr. Keeton and Pigeons, 770208 (Box 15)
    - Frank Rhodes, candidate for President of Cornell, 770209 (Box 15)
    - Views from top of Bradfield, 770210 (Box 15)
    - Doug Paine and weather station, 770211 (Box 15)
    - Women gymnasts, 770212 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Sibley interior, 770213 (Box 15)
    - Doug Shedd - hawks and chickadees, 770214 (Box 15)
    - 1776 Luncheon, 770215 (Box 15)
    - Retirement class (PREP), 770216 (Box 15)
    - Rhodes press conference, 770217 (Box 15)
    - Hotel School, 770218 (Box 15)
    - Winter scenes and traffic officer with greeting signs on booth, 770219 (Box 15)
    - F. Lee Andersen, assistant to Connie Cook, 770220 (Box 15)
    - HEPS, 770221 (Box 15)
  - March 1977
    - Winter scenes - law school, slope, museum, 770301 (Box 15)
    - "Signs of Spring" and "Spring is in the Air", 770302 (Box 15)
    - Wes, Joe, Cindy, and Connie at Arecibo (Connie), 770303 (Box 15)
    - Rhodes and Corson at Johnson Museum, 770304 (Box 15)
    - Hockey vs. Penn., 770305 (Box 15)
    - New Information Center - Day Hall, 770306 (Box 15)
    - Jim Maas & Bruce Halpern with oil painting, 770307 (Box 15)
    - Ciriaco Arroyo, prof. Of Rom. Studies, 770308 (Box 15)
    - Frozen waterfall, 770309 (Box 15)
    - Goldwin Smith interiors, 770310 (Box 15)
    - Spring scenes - Arts Quad, outdoor class, frisbee, 770311 (Box 15)
    - Dwyer Dam Bridge, 770312 (Box 15)
    - David Lyons, 770313 (Box 15)
    - Bruce Piasecki, 770314 (Box 15)
    - Jack Deal with President Corson, 770315 (Box 15)
    - Spring scenes, 770316 (Box 15)
    - Sue Cosentini, female hockey player, 770317 (Box 15)
    - Missy Mink and skunks, 770318 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes and kite flying, 770319 (Box 15)
    - Cow being milked in Willard Straight, 770320 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Goldwin Smith, Libe tower, Arts Quad in snow at night, 770321 (Box 15)
    - Green Dragon Parade, 770322 (Box 15)
    - Women's fencing team, 770323 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Balch, Baker Lab, Triphammer Bridge, Willard Straight, 770324 (Box 15)
    - Traffic signs, 770325 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes - Engineering School interiors, 770326 (Box 15)
  - April 1977
    - Work-study students aid safety patrol, 770401 (Box 15)
    - Golden phone (phoneathon), 770402 (Box 15)
    - Students and magnets, 770403 (Box 15)
    - Ruth Darling's office and Barnes Hall, 770404 (Box 15)
    - Barnes and Olin Library interiors, 770405 (Box 15)
    - Gould Colman, archivist, 770406 (Box 15)
    - Merle Lalonde - copy shot of color print, 770407 (Box 15)
    - Alumni University off campus (taken by Mike McHugh), 770408 (Box 15)
    - Bill Richards, Traffic Bureau Manager, 770409 (Box 15)
    - Removal of stump in front of Straight, 770410 (Box 15)
    - Nigerian ambassador meeting with Nigerian students at Statler Club, 770411 (Box 15)
    - New bike lock to prevent theft, 770412 (Box 15)
    - Tiddlywinks players at Willard Straight, 770413 (Box 15)
    - Stanley Idzerda, editor of Lafayette papers, at office in Olin Library, 770414 (Box 15)
    - John Amodeo (soph.) and Kira Janssen (fresh.) in Plantations Wild flower Garden, 770415 (Box 15)
    - Construction of Plant Sciences Research Building; Boyce Thompson Institute, 770416 (Box 15)
    - Spring scenes: Arts Quad, Eng. Sch. Interiors, Temple of Zeus, Goldwin Smith Interiors, 770417 (Box 15)
    - Reading room at Sage Infirmary dedicated to Nellie Corson (luncheon) (Bruce Crispell), 770418 (Box 15)
    - Two professors lecture to physics class in period garb - with antique instruments (the professors are visiting lecturers from William and Mary), 770419
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - Vet School open house, 770420 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse vs. Johns Hopkins, 770421 (Box 15)
    - Bob Gowin - 107 Stone Hall, 770422 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes and interiors: Chemistry Research Bldg., Rockefeller, Hollister, Olin Labs, Clarke Hall, Stimson, Rand, 770423
      - Contact sheet (Box 15)
    - "Anything that floats but a boat" race on Fall Creek, 770424 (Box 15)
    - Tom Gold, 770425 (Box 15)
    - Campus scenes: Architecture interiors, Uris Library interiors, students on Arts Quad (Bruce Crispell), 770426 (Box 15)
    - Rand Hall interiors, 770427 (Box 15)
    - Views from top of Barton, 770428 (Box 15)
    - Ardella Blanford, 770429 (Box 15)
    - Art class; baseball; campus scenes, 770430 (Box 15)
    - Students with marionettes for Risley Fair, 770431 (Box 15)
    - Broken statues in basement of Goldwin Smith (Prof. Peter Kuniholm), 770432 (Box 15)
    - William Paleen, Associate Director of Dean of Students in office at Balch, 770433 (Box 15)
    - Book award winners in A.D. White Reading Room, 770434 (Box 15)
    - Ken Veenema, baseball player, 770435 (Box 15)
    - Henry McPeak, 770436 (Box 15)
    - Host Program tours and spring scenes, 770437 (Box 15)
    - Spring scenes, 770438 (Box 15)
    - Art class in Franklin, 770439 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse, 770440 (Box 15)
    - Phi Psi 500 race, 770441 (Box 15)
    - Funeral wreath on Senate door, 770442 (Box 15)
    - Disibili-Day at Straight, 770443 (Box 15)
    - Students and Marionettes, 770444 (Box 15)
    - Women's Track, 770445 (Box 15)
  - May 1977
    - Women's baseball, 770501 (Box 16)
    - Carl Sagan, 770502 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes: Interiors - McGraw, Morrill, Plant Sci.; Exteriors - Straight, Quad., Tower, Goldwin Smith, Ag. Quad., 770503
      - Contact sheet (Box 16)
    - Interiors - Plant Science, Food Science; Exteriors - Ag. Quad., 770504 (Box 16)
    - Crew, 770505 (Box 16)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 770506 (Box 16)
    - Morrill Hall interiors, Campus Store interiors, Baker Lab exteriors, rain, 770507 (Box 16)
    - Springfest, 770508 (Box 16)
    - Risley Fair, 770509 (Box 16)
    - Ag. Engineering, 770510 (Box 16)
    - Psychology - Videotaping center (Uris Hall), 770511 (Box 16)
    - Carl Sagan in office, 770512 (Box 16)
    - Tennis, 770513 (Box 16)
    - Don Greenberg and computer graphics, 770514 (Box 16)
    - Views from Law School tower, 770515 (Box 16)
    - Goldwin smith auditoriums and A.D. White House - for Scoones, 770516 (Box 16)
    - Paul McKeegan retirement party, 770517 (Box 16)
    - Ruth Darling retirement party, 770518 (Box 16)
    - Final exams in Barton, 770519 (Box 16)
    - Baseball, 770520 (Box 16)
    - President Corson addresses faculty for last time, 770521 (Box 16)
    - Floyd Newman display case reshot, 770522 (Box 16)
    - Old winter shot of Straight, 770523 (Box 16)
  - June 1977
    - Untitled (Box 16)
    - James L. Elliott (Radiophysics Space Research) "Uranis", 770602 (Box 16)
    - Commencement - May 30, 1977, 770603 (Box 16)
    - Information Center Display Case - Cap & Gown, 770604 (Box 16)
    - President & Mrs. Corson with Earl Flansburgh (model train), 770605 (Box 16)
    - Annabel Taylor, 770606 (Box 16)
    - Alumni University - Ornithology, 770607 (Box 16)
    - Laurel & Mike Kintner, 770608 (Box 16)
    - Severinghaus family at commencement Clare Booth Luce also in picture, 770609 (Box 16)
    - President Corson's album, 770610 (Box 16)
    - Gustav J. Requardt - Class of '09, 770611 (Box 16)
    - Aquavet - Woods Hole - Russ, 770612 (Box 16)
    - Professor Goldstein - Chemistry; Baker Lab. - Lots of interiors, 770613 (Box 16)
    - Aerial - Color Internegative of Information Center Aerial R B - F4, 770614 (Box 16)
    - Reunion - 1977, 770615 (Box 16)
  - July 1977
    - Floyd Newman display case (collection) in Barton, 770701 (Box 16)
    - Cornellians & Cornell - Title, 770702 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes, 770703 (Box 16)
    - Model Cities - Russ, 770704 (Box 16)
  - August 1977
    - Campus Scenes - Sol, 770801 (Box 16)
    - Pres. Corson - Book Dedication (Bruce), 770802 (Box 16)
    - CAU SUMMER, 770803 (Box 16)
    - CAU SUMMER, 770804 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes, 770805 (Box 16)
    - Knapp - planes for weather studies, 770806 (Box 16)
    - William G. Herbster - Sr. Vice President, 770807 (Box 16)
    - Ithaca Commons - Russ, 770808 (Box 16)
    - Campus Scenes - Bruce, 770809 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes tours Geneva, 770810 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes tours libraries, 770811 (Box 16)
    - Campus scenes from Clark Hall, 770812 (Box 16)
    - Alumni Archives Cane with signatures, 770813 (Box 16)
    - B/w copies of 3 slides sent on Voyager, 770814 (Box 16)
    - Helicopter & radar - Bruce & Russ, 770815 (Box 16)
    - Campus scenes - Russ (good Ag. Quad shot!), 770816 (Box 16)
    - Freshman Offbeat Olympics, 770817 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes at Convocation, 770818 (Box 16)
    - Football field painting, 770819 (Box 16)
    - Orientation Week, 770820 (Box 16)
    - Sage Dining Reopening, 770821 (Box 16)
    - Campus scenes, 770822 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes at Synchrotron, 770823 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes at Clark Hall, 770824 (Box 16)
    - Rock garden in front of Thurston; mopeds, 770825 (Box 16)
  - September 1977
    - Rhodes meeting freshmen on Arts Quad (Fun in the Sun Festival), 770901 (Box 16)
    - Boyce Thompson construction; Arts Quad (Olin Library) at night, 770902 (Box 16)
    - Rock garden in front of Thurston, 770903 (Box 16)
    - Sage Dining, renovated interior, 770904 (Box 16)
    - Rare book collection on witchcraft; Arts Quad (contrast 1873 pic.), 770905 (Box 16)
    - Isle of Shoals (Robey), 770905A (Box 16)
    - new wheelchair ramp at Olin Library; sculpture installation at Johnson Museum, 770906 (Box 16)
    - new COSEP officers, 770907 (Box 16)
    - test roll HP5-1600, 770908 (Box 16)
    - Connie Bart; Michael Kammen, 770909 (Box 16)
    - Campus scenes from Clark Hall, 770910 (Box 16)
    - Professor J.M. Elliot's Animal Science 100 class at Livestock Judging Pavillion, 770911 (Box 16)
    - John M. Echols/book dedication, 770912 (Box 16)
    - Art Museum class, 770913 (Box 16)
    - Rhodes at football practice, 770914 (Box 16)
    - Development, 770915 (Box 16)
    - Cornell vs. Colgate (football), 770916 (Box 16)
    - Ben Mintz 2nd retirement party (Sol), 770917 (Box 16)
    - Dr. Greg Williams, 770918 (Box 16)
    - Art Museum; campus scenes, 770919 (Box 16)
    - Thomas Smith, Truman Scholarship winner, 770920 (Box 16)
    - June Franklin & Joan Hart, workers for United Way Fund Drive, 770921 (Box 16)
    - Pres. Rhodes in electric car and geology rock garden, 770922 (Box 16)
    - Pres. Rhodes Press Conference, 770923 (Box 16)
    - ETV Center Chemistry Broadcast, 770924 (Box 16)
    - Architecture Old Boys' Reunion, 770925 (Box 16)
    - Baker Lab renovations, 770926 (Box 16)
    - Milton Friedman's lecture, 770927 (Box 16)
    - United Way rally, 770928 (Box 16)
    - views of Cornell from west shore, 770929 (Box 16)
    - Johnson Museum, 770930 (Box 16)
    - Rutgers vs. Cornell football, 770931 (Box 16)
    - Bullis Room dedication (A.D. White House) (Sol), 770932 (Box 16)
  - October 1977
    - Johnson Art Museum, 771001 (Box 16)
    - Trustee Council, 771002 (Box 16)
    - campus scenes, 771003 (Box 16)
    - infrared campus scenes, 771004 (Box 16)
    - Japanese administrators meet Pres. Rhodes and Cornell, 771005 (Box 16)
    - Fall campus scenes, 771006 (Box 16)